Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory6 Mss.B.B61.inventory06
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents H
  - Hampson, Thomas (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 13
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 31
  - Hampton, L.S. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 3; 2p.
  - Hamson, Charles C. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 5; 2p.
  - Hamy, Theodore Jules Ernest (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 18; Obits
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 21; Obits
  - Hancock, J.A. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1894 Jan. 22; 1p.
  - Hand, Learned (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 4; 2p.
  - Handbook of the American Indians, Suggestions for republication (Box 36)
    - See Moorehead, W.K., Sept. 20, 1935
  - Handbook of North American Languages (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1907
  - Handler, Milton (Box 36)
    - See Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas, Feb. 11, 1937
  - Handlirsch, Anton (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1926 May 6; 1p.
  - Handy, W.C. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 16; 1p.
  - Hane, T.E. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1916 May 26
    - To Boas, 1916 May 25
  - Hanin? (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 15
  - Hanks, L.M., Jr. (Box 36)
    - L.M. Hanks, Jr. -- from M.I. Finkelstein, 1942 June 4
  - Hanley, J.R. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 2; 1p.
  - Hanna, George W. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 28
  - Hansen, Alexander F. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 5; 2p.
  - Hansen, Andreas (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 7; 2p.
    - A. Hansen -- from Koy, 1931 Dec.
  - Hansen, E. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 27; 1p.
  - Hansome, Marius (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 29; 2p.
  - Hantzsch, Bernard (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 17; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec.; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 1; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 29; 10p.
    - To Boas, 1908 May 9; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1908 May 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 18; 8p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 22; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Sept. 3; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Sept. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909
  - Hapfel, J. Chr. G. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, E.L., 1906 Jan. 13; 1p.
  - Hapgood, Norman (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 2; 2p.
  - Harand, Irene (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - See Mead, Nelson P., Nov. 15, 1939
  - Harand-Bewegung (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 8; 2p.
  - Harap, Louis (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1942 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Apr. 4; 2p.
  - Harcourt, A. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1920 May 17; 1p.
  - Harcourt Brace Publishers (Box 36)
    - See Hamilton, 1936 June 5; 1p.
  - Harcourt, Brace & Howe (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 21; 1p.
  - Harcourt, R. d' (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1927 June 11; 2p.
  - Hardie, G.R. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 24; 1p.
  - Hare? G.E. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 20
  - Hargraves, L.L. (Box 36)
    - To Boas
    - See Haury, E.W., Mar. 2, 1927
  - Harkness, Mrs. (Box 36)
    - See Boas, F., Apr. 17, 1930
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 14; 2p.
  - Harkness, L.K. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1930 May 10; 4p.
  - Harlem Interracial Forum (Box 36)
    See Thompson, Anna
  - Harles, Heinrich (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 14; 1p.
  - Harlon, Edgar R. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 13
  - Harlow, Rex F. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 11; 1p.
  - Harms, Ernst (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 3; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 24; 1p.
  - Harnack, A. von (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1920 Jan. 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 13; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 7; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 15; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 7; postcard
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 3; 2p.
  - Harnack Ueber Die Notlage der Deutschen Wissenschaft (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 1; 1p.
  - Harned, Florence (Mrs. W.E.) (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 16; 1p.
  - Harper, George McLean (Box 36)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938
  - Harper, Robert Almer (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 June 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 June 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 June 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 13; 1p.
  - Harper, William R. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1894 Mar. 19
    - From Boas, 1903 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 8; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Jan. 13; 1p.
  - Harper's Magazine (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 16; 1p.
  - Harralee, C.F. (Box 36)
    - To Boas, 1907 June 13
  - Harriman, E.H. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 19; 1p.
  - Harriman, G.E. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 20; 1p.
  - Harrington, John P. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1927 May 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 May 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Sept. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Sept. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 22; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 June 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 June 30; Telegram
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 24; 1p. (2 copies)
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 May 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 27; telegram
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 15; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Sept. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - J.P. Harrington -- to E.C. Deloria, 1939 May 6; 2p.
    - J.P. Harrington -- to J.W. Powell, 1906 Apr. 6
    - J.P. Harrington -- to Tozzer, 1908 Oct. 24; 2p.
  - Harrington, M.R. (Box 36)
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 6
  - Harris (Box 37)
    - See Boas, F. (open letter), Dec. 29, 1933
  - Harris, Abram L. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 June 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 9; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 30; 1p.
  - Harris, B. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p.
  - Harris, E. Richard (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 8; 1p.
  - Harris, H.S. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 18
  - Harris, Jack (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 15; 1p.
  - Harris, Mark (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1942 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 17; 1p.
  - Harris, Mrs. Mark (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 14; 1p.
  - Harris, N.D. (Box 37)
    - N.D. Harris -- to Keppel, 1907 Feb. 1
    - N.D. Harris -- to A.W. Phillips, 1907 Feb. 1
  - Harris, Seale (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1919 June 18; 1p.
  - Harris, T.L. (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 2; 1p.
  - Harris, William Torrey (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1903 July 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 July 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1895 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1903 May 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 July 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 July 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 1; 1p.
  - Harris, Zellig S. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Aug. 2; 1p.
  - Harrison, C.C. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1910 June 25
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 8
  - Harrison, F. (Box 37)
    - F. Harrison -- From E.C. Pickering, 1919 Mar. 19; 2p.
  - Harrison, McVeigh (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 26; 1p.
  - Harrison, Ross G. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 June 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 18; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 5; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 3; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 4; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 19
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - See Kennelly, A.E., Mar. 7, 1936
    - R.G. Harrison -- to Stephen P. Duggan, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - (Attached to letter of from Duggan, Stephan P. to Boas, F.), April 12, 1920
  - Harrow, B. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 1; 1p.
      (Enc: Sample of letter to be sent to American scientists.)
    - See Prager, W.L., May 25, 1933
  - Harrson (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 22
  - Hart, A.C. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1910 May 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 May 9
    - From Boas, 1910 May 24
    - From Boas, 1910 June 4
    - From Boas, 1910 June 17
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 1
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 6
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 13
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 18; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 19
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 7; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1910 May 19
    - To Boas, 1910 May 23
    - To Boas, 1910 May 26
    - To Boas, 1910 June 1
    - To Boas, 1910 June 2
    - To Boas, 1910 June 6
    - To Boas, 1910 June 16
    - To Boas, 1910 June 28
    - To Boas, 1910 July 6
    - To Boas, 1910 July 29
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 4
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1916 Apr. 20
    - A.C. Hart -- from C.L. Carrick, 1910 Aug. 11
    - A.C. Hart -- from C.L. Carrick, 1910 Aug. 11
  - Hart, G. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 31
  - Hart, Walter Morris (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 22; 1p.
  - Harter, J.R. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1937 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 17; 1p.
  - Hartland, E.S. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 30; 1p.
  - Hartman, C.V. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 27
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 26
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 13
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 7
    - From Boas, 1910 May 25
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Feb. 27; 2p
      - ?Sept. 7, 1912 on back of Boas to Seler, 1912 Sep. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 26 and Oct. 17
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 June 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 22; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 23; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 4
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 7
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1907 May 19
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1910 May 12; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1910 June 13
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 18; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1911 May 18; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Sept. 15
    - To Boas, 1911 Sept. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 30; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 July 25
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1914 Sept. 27
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept.9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Oct. 15; telegram
    - C.V. Hartman -- to M.H. Saville, 1919 Nov. 18; 4p.
  - Hartman, J.P. (Box 37)
    - J.P. Hartman -- to Columbia Univ. Museum.Curator, 1930 Aug. 16; 2p.
    - (Attached to Fackenthal, F.D. to Hartman, J.P., Aug. 22, 1930)
    - J.P. Hartman -- from Fackenthal, F.D., 1930 Aug. 22
  - Hartmann, G.W. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 6; 1p.
  - Hartmann, Waldemar (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1930 Aug. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 18; 1p.
  - Hartog, Alfred (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 20; 1p.
  - Hartog, P. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 28; 1p.
  - Hartwell, Edward M. (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1891 May 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1893 Aug. 17; 3p.
  - Harvard Trust Co. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 2; 1p.
  - Harvard University - Germanic Museum (Box 37)
    See Francke, Kuno
  - Harvard University. Librarian (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1925 June 2; 1p.
  - Harvard University Press (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 31; 1p.
  - Harvey, George -- From Boas, 1909 Mar. 6 (Box 37)
  - Harvey, H.L. (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 19
  - Harvey, M. (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1888 Feb. 18; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1890 Sept. 11
  - Harvey, W.B. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 25; 1p.
  - H.L. Harvey & Co. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 29
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 19; 1p.
  - Haseltine, Charles F., Jr. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 22
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 14
    - C.F. Haseltine -- from Columbia Univ., 1906 Dec. 4
  - Haskell, Edward (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 5; 1p.
  - Haskell, Henry S. (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1925 May 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 14; 1p.
  - Haskell, Mrs. Henry (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 24; 1p.
  - Haskin, Leslie L. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1922 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 28; 1p.
  - Hassenstein, B. (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1885 Oct. 26; 3p.
  - Hassler, Dr. E. (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1894 June 6; 1p.
  - Hastings, James (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 7
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept. 28
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1906 June 1
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 22
  - Hastings, O.C. (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1895 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1895 Mar. 6
  - Hatch, Julia E. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 3; 1p.
  - Hatfield, James Taft (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 31; 2p.
  - Hatt, G. (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 5
    - G. Hatt -- to J.A. Teit, 1917 Apr. 15; 3p.
  - Haug, Gotthold (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 6
  - Haupt, H. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 31; 1p.
  - Haupt, Paul (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1914 Sept. 24
    - From Boas, 1914 Sept. 28
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1920 July 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 22; 1p.
  - Haury, E.W. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 2; 1p.
  - Hauser, Alois (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 29; 2p.
  - Hauser, Karl (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 20; 1p.
  - Haushofer, K.E.N. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 8; 1p.
  - Hausknecht, Ludwik (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1942 May 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 24; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Apr. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1942 June 8; 2p.
  - Hauthal, R. (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1923 Dec. 9; 1p.
  - Havana University (Box 37)
    - From the law students, 1921 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - To Dean from the general assn. of Students of medicine, 1921 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - See Mencia, D., 1921 Nov. 22
  - Havemeyer, T.A. (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 20; 1p.
  - Havemeyer, Mrs. (Box 37)
    - See Boas, F. to Cadman, S.P., May 29,1933
  - Havens, V.L. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 13; 3p.
  - Haver, F. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 1; 1p.
  - Hawes, Charles H. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 29
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - (See: Boas, F. to Tyler, J.M. Nov. 13, 1919), 1920 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 24
  - Hawkes, E.W. (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 25
    - E.W. Hawkes -- from F.W. Hodge, 1913 Dec. 10
  - Hawkes, Herbert Edwin (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 21; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - (Enc: Hawkes, open letter n.d.), 1919 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 18; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Dec.; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Columbia Univ. Multigraph Dept. bill, Nov. 22, 1919)
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - Hawkes, -- to anon (open letter), 1931 Feb.; 1p.
      - (Enc. with Boas, F. to Hawkes, Oct. 31, 1919)
  - Hawkes, J. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 17; 1p.
  - Hawley, E.H. (Box 37)
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 16
  - Hay, C.L. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 July 30; 2p.
  - Hayden, Philip M. (Box 37)
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 June 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 June 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 June 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 July 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 May 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 July 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 July 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 July 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 10; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec.; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 May 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 June 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 July 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 July 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 May 31; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr.; 1p.
    - (Enc: List), 1941 Oct. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Sept. 17; 2p.
    - (Enc: 5p. of Dr. Boas' figuring), 1928 Nov. 9
    - (budget Statement), 1928 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 July 28; 2p.
    - (Enc. Columbia Univ. Dept. of Anthropology. Budget 1930-31.), 1931 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 17; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 July 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 June 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - (Enc: Thompson, N.S. to Butler, N.S. Mar. 17, 1933), 1933 Mar. 24; 1p.